他有点晚了
He's a little late.
我们早一点着陆  长官
We landed a bit early, sir.
你信任这个家伙  少校
You trust this guy, major?
我从未见过他
I've never seen him.
美国情报机构称他是冠军
U.S. Intelligence says he's a champion.
你可以称之为  好德国人
What you might call a "good German."
全靠他的寂寞
All by his lonesome.
美丽的
Beautiful.
看…
Look...
我们不能让他们活着
we can't let them take him alive.
走吧
Let's go.
Twenty-four twenty.
20420什么  上尉
Twenty-four twenty what, captain?
他想告诉你一些事情
He was trying to tell you something.
你一定认识到路德维希船长
You do realize that Captain Ludwig
是卡纳里斯上将的私人工作人员
was on the personal staff of Admiral Canaris
管道进入德国海军情报局
and the pipeline into German naval intelligence?
他也是我父亲在战争前的亲密私人朋友
He was also a close personal friend of my father's before the war.
哦  也许你们两个应该把他留在海军上将的队伍里
Oh, maybe you two should have left him on the admiral's staff.
不  我们不能那样做
No, we couldn't do that.
他的信息太重要了  我们得设法把他救出来
His information was too important. We had to try to get him out.
二十
Twenty?
对你有什么意义  克拉克  不
Mean anything to you, Clark? No.
但我已经把它传递给了英国和自由的法国情报机构
But I've passed it on to British and Free French intelligence.
当我们到达伦敦时  他们可能会给我们一些东西
They may have something for us when we get to London.
轻松  女孩  你不能离开没有矮子
Easy, girl, you can't leave without Shorty.
中尉  你认为你能支持我们吗
Lieutenant, do you think you could back up and get us out of this?
现在  抓住它  我们的家伙有一个很棒的左手
Now, hold it. Our guy's got a great left hand.
有人做某事
Somebody do something!
让我走  典型的士兵的行为
Let me go. Typical enlisted men's behaviour.
在酒吧打架自杀
Getting themselves killed in a bar fight
对一些妓女的偏爱
over the questionable favours of some street whore.
我不能同意你更多的意见  先生
I couldn't agree with you more, sir.
少校  我听到你说的对吗
Do I hear you right, major?
你  失败者的冠军
You, the champion of the underdog?
嗯  你知道  一个流浪汉和一个穿着制服的醉汉仍然是个流浪汉和醉鬼  先生
Well, you know, a bum and a drunk in uniform is still a bum and a drunk, sir.
肖蒂  你还好吗
Shorty? You okay?
-你们在干什么  冠军  帮我一把
- What are you guys doing? - Champ, give me a hand.
把它放在那儿
Hold it there.
坚持住  伙计们
Hold it there, men.
打破它  我马上就回来
Break it up. I'll be back in a minute.
我要逮捕那些人
I want those men arrested.
你想逮捕他们
You want them arrested?
是啊  我敢打赌一个月的工资  他们今天早上在警卫室里
Yeah. I'll bet a month's salary that they were in the guardhouse this morning.
我只是想确保他们今晚回到警卫室
I just want to make sure they're back in the guardhouse tonight.
你看见那个大家伙了吗
You see that big guy?
也得到了一个地狱般的权利
Got a hell of a right too.
我们下一个任务很方便
Come in very handy on our next mission.
原谅我  将军  但是我认为少校的任务太多了
Forgive me, general, but I think the major's gone on one mission too many.
不  上校  还没有
No, colonel, not yet.
不仅如此
Not just yet.
从德国最高司令部的观点来看
In the viewpoint of the German High Command,
日本未能在珍珠港取得胜利
the Japanese failed to follow up their victory at Pearl Harbour
而且现在不被认为是值得信赖的盟友
and are not now considered to be trustworthy allies.
他们也意识到盟军战争的努力现在是完全专注的
They are also aware that the Allied war effort is now totally dedicated
粉碎德国  然后转向日本
to crushing Germany before turning to the Japanese.
最高指挥官认为战争可能会持续几年
The High Command feels the war might go on for years
德国仍有可能输掉这场战争
and that Germany could still conceivably lose the war.
现在  那些将军们并不急于和他们分享这一切
Now, those generals were in no rush to share all this with the f黨rer.
保持自己的活力
Keeping themselves alive, sort of.
对
Yes.
最终  他们吞下了他们的容貌骄傲
Ultimately, they swallowed their Junker pride,
他们就把这句话传给这个人：
and they took the word to this man:
Kurt Richter将军
SS General Kurt Richter,
一个希特勒暗暗信任的人
a man whom Hitler has come to trust implicitly.
他们使李希特相信这是他的职责
They convinced Richter that it was his duty
把真相告诉被告
to inform the f黨rer about the truth.
他这样做了
He did so.
但他也对F的下一个问题提出了答案：
But he also worked out an answer to the f黨rer's next question:
德国如何确保最后胜利
"How does Germany ensure a final victory?"
确切地  用瓦尔基里行动
Exactly. With Operation Valkyrie.
第四帝国  先生们
The Fourth Reich, gentlemen.
李希特想出了一个清单
Richter had come up with a list
十几个男人  所有德国顶级天才
of a dozen men, all top German geniuses
在政府  科学  军事  警察  教育方面
in government, science, the military, police, education.
他们都在35岁以下
All of them under 35
他们都是忠诚的纳粹分子
and all of them loyal Nazis.
新影子政府的存在
The existence of this new shadow government
由我们在德国海军情报局的联络员证实
was confirmed by our contacts in the German naval intelligence.
在过去的几个月里
In the past few months
包围斯大林格勒的德军投降了
the German army surrounding Stalingrad has surrendered
美国海军在太平洋上仍然是不可战胜的
and the U.S. Navy remains unbeatable in the Pacific.
F R已经做出了决定
The f黨rer has made the decision.
这12个人
These 12 men
站在旁边  被召唤到德国的慕尼黑  一时间通知
are standing by to be summoned to Munich, Germany at a moment's notice.
从那里  他们将继续乘火车
From there, they will go on by train
沿着现在悬挂的东方快车的路线
along the route of the now suspended Orient Express.
威尼斯  的里雅斯特  贝尔格莱德  索非亚…
Venice, Trieste, Belgrade, Sofia...
最后  伊斯坦布尔
and finally, Istanbul.
在那里  他们将建立
And there, they will establish
超过10年  20  一个世纪  如果必要的话
over 10 years, 20, a century, if necessary
整个中东…
all over the Middle East...
新的第四帝国
the new Fourth Reich.
你将招收12名普通犯人
You will tak e 12 general prisoners
判处死刑  或者长期监禁
convicted and sentenced to death or to long terms of imprisonment.
你将训练和鉴定囚犯
You will train and qualify the prisoners
然后秘密地把他们送来
and deliver them secretly behind the lines.
你会攻击并摧毁你指定的目标
You will attack and destroy your assigned target.
任何违反安全的行为
Any breach of security,
任何纪律的失败
any failure of discipline,
囚犯们马上回到他们来的地方
and the prisoners go right back where they came from
对句子的简易执行
for summary execution of sentence.
我想单独和Stern谈谈
I want to speak to Private Stern alone.
这是命令
That's an order.
你在找另一个肮脏的人吗  少校
You looking for another Dirty Dozen, major?
不  不  不  我只是在等待时间  直到我成为将军
No, no, no. I'm just biding my time until I become general
让战争结束  现在发生了什么事
and get the war over. Now, what happened?
和酒吧里的一个军官打架
Got into a fight with an officer in a bar.
打他
Hit him.
摔断了下巴  把他送到了医院
Broke his jaw, sent him to the hospital.
哦  那太精明了  他说了什么让你不高兴
Oh, that's very shrewd. Now, what did he say to upset you?
我们开始讨论种族问题
We got into a discussion about race.
我告诉他他属于另一边
I told him he belonged on the other side.
我懂了  所以你又回到了一个军事监狱
I see. So you wind up in a military prison again
你面临另一个军事法庭  现在  看
and you're facing another court-martial. Now, look.
你知道的
You know...
我会给你一个机会打败这一切  回到战争中去
I'll give you a chance to beat this thing and get back to the war.
您说什么  你想要还是不想要
What do you say? Do you want it or not?
我不知道  少校
I don't know, major.
你会杀了很多人
You get a lot of men killed.
你杀了很多好人
You kill a lot of good people.
我再也不知道这对你来说是好事还是坏事
And I don't know anymore whether it's good versus evil with you.
也许这只是邪恶与邪恶
Maybe it's just evil versus evil.
我去找你的管理员
I'll find your keeper.
走吧
Let's go!
少校  跟我一起散步
Take a walk with me, major.
我有一些重要的信息要告诉你
I've got some important information for you.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
早上好  中尉
Nice morning, lieutenant.
对  是的  是的
Yes. Yes, it is.
你为将军工作  是吗  这是正确的
You work for the general, huh? That's right.
你以前和莱特少校在一起吗
You've been with Major Wright before?
这是正确的  我又回来了
That's right. And I made it back.
战争结束了  中尉
War's over for me, lieutenant.
嗯  我不会说战争已经结束了  嗯
Well, I wouldn't say that the war is altogether over for you, hmm.
不是战争地狱吗  中尉
Ain't war hell, lieutenant?
当德国人在1918投降的时候
And when the Germans surrendered in 1918,
法国人把他们带到一辆火车车厢里
the French brought them down to a railroad car
在密西西比的森林里
in the forest of Compi間ne.
恐怕我还没来得及
Little bit before my time, I'm afraid.
当法国人在1940投降的时候
And when the French surrendered in 1940,
希特勒从老东方快车上订购了同一辆铁路车
Hitler ordered that same railroad car from the old Orient Express
回到同样的地点
brought back to the exact same spot.
哦  法国人这次能感觉到刺刀了吗
Oh, so that the French could feel the bayonet this time?
确切地  那辆车是2419号
Exactly. Now, that car was number 2419
现在在柏林
and it's in Berlin right now.
现在  我们的想法是
Now, the thinking is
那些德国人会炸掉那该死的东西
that those Germans will blow up that damn thing
在他们再次投降之前
before they'd ever surrender in it again.
但是怎么办呢
But how does?
2419后2420
After 2419 comes 2420.
新第四帝国的开国元勋
The founding fathers of the new Fourth Reich
将在伊斯坦布尔2420号车到达
will arrive in Istanbul in car number 2420.
现在我们知道这辆车在哪里了吗  坎贝尔上尉来了
Now we know where this car is now? Lt. Campbell's come up
一些新的空气侦察照片表明
with some new air recon photos that indicates
他们可能藏在慕尼黑的一个火车场里
they may be hidden in a train yard in Munich.
坎贝尔中尉显然是一位非常聪明的年轻女士
Lieutenant Campbell apparently is a very bright young lady.
为什么  她很聪明
Why, she's brilliant.
你知道  她是在这个德国贵族长大的
You know, she grew up in this German aristocracy
因为她的父亲是一名外交服务人员30年
because her father was a Foreign Service officer for 30 years.
该死  Marshal Rommel过去常在膝盖上弹她
Hell, Marshal Rommel used to bounce her on his knee.
在她18岁之前还是之后
Before or after she turned 18?
现在  现在
Now, now.
德姆丘克  Dravko  绞死
Demchuk, Dravko. Death by hanging.
达格斯蒂诺  卡迈恩
D'Agostino, Carmine.
绞死
Death by hanging.
Collins…
Collins...
弗雷德里克
Frederick.
未被判刑的
Unsentenced.
里基茨  汤姆
Ricketts, Tom.
未被判刑的
Unsentenced.
汉密尔顿或哈密尔顿  约瑟夫
Hamilton, Joseph.
绞死
Death by hanging.
霍夫曼  托马斯  五十年的艰苦劳动
Hoffman, Thomas. Fifty years' hard labour.
Wilson  Lonnie  四十年的艰苦劳动
Wilson, Lonnie. Forty years' hard labour.
埃切瓦里  罗伯托
Echevarria, Roberto.
五十年的艰苦劳动
Fifty years' hard labour.
回到正轨
Get back in line.
少校说还会有一个
The major said there would be one more.
嗯  也许少校错了
Well, maybe the major was wrong.
那么我们就没有一打了
We don't have a dozen, then.
嘿  Joey  嘿  Stern
- Hey, Joey. - Hey, Stern.
你真倒霉  不是吗  乔
Pushing your luck, aren't you, Joe?
好的
All right.
叶的信仰如此渺小
Ye of such little faith.
Stern  约瑟夫
Stern, Joseph.
未被判刑的
Unsentenced.
Demchuk  你开始当火车司机回家了
You started off as a train engineer back home, Demchuk.
你知道  这种天赋可能会再次派上用场
You know, that talent may come in handy again.
我是个好工程师  先生
I was good engineer, sir.
嗯
Uh-huh.
是的  但是在你结束这趟火车之前
Yeah, but before you handed the train in at the end of the day,
你开始抢劫乘客
you started robbing passengers.
我也是个火车强盗  长官
I was good train robber too, sir.
你要抢火车吗  少校  哦  不  不  不
You want to rob a train, major? Oh, no, no, no.
我想阻止一个人  挑一些坏人
I want to stop one and pick off some bad people.
我一生中挑了很多坏人
I pick off lots of bad people in my life.
我敢打赌  Dravko  我敢打赌你有
I bet you have, Dravko. I just bet you have.
好的  Holt
All right, Holt.
到底是怎么回事  中士
What the hell is going on, sergeant?
我不知道  先生  我们通常只有在悬挂的时候才能得到这个
I don't know, sir. We usually only get this when there's a hanging.
汉弥尔顿有枪  对吧  这是正确的
Hamilton's got a gun, right? That's right.
打倒了议员们  守着它  把我们钉了下来
Knocked out the MPs guarding it and pinned us down.
我们可能不得不杀了那个男孩  哦  这可能需要一些帮助
We may have to kill that boy. Oh, that may take some doing.
他杀死了一个白人妇女
He killed a white woman.
他哪儿也找不到
He's not getting anywhere.
现在我们拿到了那辆装甲卡车  如果他想下来  我们会把他炸开的
Now we got that armoured truck back there. We'll blow him apart if he tries to get down.
你打算怎么办  炸毁监狱杀死囚犯
What are you gonna do? Blow up a prison to kill a prisoner?
谁在跟他说话  跟他说话
Who's been talking to him? Talking to him?
没错  跟他说话
That's right, talking to him.
现在你看  我要去那里做个交易
Now you look, I'm gonna go up there and make a deal.
我也要许下诺言
And I'm also gonna make a promise.
一定不要弄坏它  你明白吗
Make sure you don't break it. Do you understand?
你明白了
You got it.
汉弥尔顿
Hamilton?
汉密尔顿或哈密尔顿  这是Major Wright
Hamilton, this is Major Wright.
你知道我是谁  我知道你是谁
You know who I am and I know who you are.
汉弥尔顿
Hamilton?
我想和你谈谈
I wanna talk to you.
我最好现在就死
I'm better off dying right here and now.
我会有很多陪伴的
I'll have a lot of company.
现在  你急死了什么
Now, what's your rush in dying?
说话不能失去任何东西
You can't lose anything by talking.
可以
Okay.
那就来吧
Come ahead, then.
好吧  我要跟你打电话  汉弥尔顿
All right, I'm gonna lay it on the line with you, Hamilton.
我仍然可以使用一个可以突破安全单元的人
I can still use a man who can break out of a maximum-security cell,
站起来
get up there,
拿一把机关枪
and grab a machine gun.
几乎一路领先
Almost made it all the way.
据我所知  你还没有杀死一个MP
As far as I know, you haven't killed an MP
你无论如何都要绞死
and you're gonna hang anyway
不仅仅是
for a lot more than just
企图逃跑
an attempted escape.
你到底想从我这里得到什么
So, what the hell do you want from me?
你为什么杀了你的妻子
Why did you kill your wife?
管好你自己的事
Just mind your own business.
我在巴黎见过她
I met her in Paris.
战争爆发了
Then the war came.
我们到达伦敦
We made it to London.
于是我回到美国参军
So I went back to the U.S. To join the Army.
伙计  我打破了我的屁股回到这里
Man, I broke my butt to get back over here.
然后我去了她的公寓
Then I went to her apartment.
她和一位皇家空军船长住在一起
She was living with an RAF captain.
他拔出枪说：  黑鬼在英国不受欢迎
He pulled a gun and said, "Niggers ain't welcome in Britain."
然后她笑了
And then she laughed.
她笑了
She laughed.
你为什么不放下枪呢  投降  我向你保证…
Why don't you put down your gun. Surrender and I promise you...
早上你会和那些人一起训练
you'll be training with the men in the morning.
军队不会让你遵守诺言的
Army ain't gonna let you keep that promise.
哦  是的  他们会的  他们需要我  我有消息告诉你：
Oh, yes, they will. They need me, and I got news for you:
他们也需要你
They need you too.
还有像你一样的11个邋遢鬼
Along with 11 other slobs just like you.
可以
Okay.
好吧  你想怎么做
Okay, how you wanna work it?
你指出  30口径的下限…
You point that.30 calibre downrange...
你跟着我回家
and you follow me home.
好的
All right.
大家排好队  数一数
Everybody line up and count off.
一  二
- One. - Two.
-三  -四
- Three. - Four.
-五  -六
- Five. - Six.
-七  -八
- Seven. - Eight.
-九  -十
- Nine. - Ten.
-十一  -十二
- Eleven. - Twelve.
好的
All right.
现在  通过你的出现  你已经表现出强烈的愿望
Now, by your presence, you've indicated a strong desire
自愿参加这个任务  这给了你三条路
to volunteer for this mission, which leaves you three ways to go.
训练时你会犯规
You can foul up during training,
在这种情况下  你将被送回监狱执行死刑
in which case you'll be sent back to prison for execution of sentence.
二  我的意思是  你可以在行动中犯规…
Two, I mean, you can foul up in action...
在这种情况下  我会亲自炸掉你的脑袋
in which case I will personally blow your brains out.
或者你可以做你被告知的事
Or you can do what you're told,
在这种情况下  你可以通过
in which case, you may just get by.
现在  如果你们中的任何人试图逃跑…
Now, if any one of you tries to escape...
你们将被送回执行死刑
you'll all be sent back for execution of sentence.
因此  你们都是互相依赖的
Therefore, you're all dependent on one another.
如果有人试图变得聪明
And if anybody tries to get smart,
你都会头脑清醒的  对吧
you'll all get it right in the head, right?
正确的
Right.
现在  由于这次任务的偶然性
Now, due to the contingency nature of this mission
汉弥尔顿私人关系的恶化
and the deteriorating relations between Private Hamilton
以及福布斯路监狱的工作人员和下院议员…
and the staff and the MPs of Forbes Road Prison...
你被派到这里去了
you've been sent out here into the field
训练的性质也在加强
and the nature of your training has been intensified.
埃克维拉里亚
"Ekkevarria."
埃切瓦里  先生
Echevarria, sir.
拿起我的手跟着我
Pick up my grips and follow me.
好的  把他们送回兵营
All right. Have them sent back to the barracks.
是的  先生  好吧
Yes, sir. All right!
每个人都进入兵营
Everybody into the barracks.
如果你有什么可抱怨的
If you have something to complain about,
牧师的时间在4到5之间  走吧
the chaplain's hours are between 4 and 5. Let's go.
击中它
Hit it!
埃切瓦里  你对我来说是个谜  我查过你的档案了
Echevarria, you're a mystery to me. I went through your files.
你已经经历了一些相当沉重的事情
You've been through some pretty heavy stuff.
抢劫  一个黑帮绑架  用致命武器袭击
Robbery, a gangland kidnapping, assault with a deadly weapon.
我的童年很糟糕  先生
I had a very bad childhood, sir.
嗯  我想出了类似的方法
Well, I figured something like that.
但直到那天晚上你从英格兰银行撤出
But until you made that night withdrawal from the Bank of England
用A.45和一点炸药…
with a.45 and a little dynamite...
你没有做过什么艰苦的事  是吗
you haven't done any heavy time, have you?
我总是表示真诚的悔恨  先生
I always express sincere remorse, sir.
当然可以
Sure you do.
我是说  假释官  法官…
I mean, parole officers, judges...
连警察都想让你休息一下
even cops wanted to give you a break.
嗯  伙计…我是说  少校
Well, man... I mean, major.
我总是想  当你去做的时候  全力以赴
I always figure, when you're going for it, go all out.
当你走在大街上时  你要发疯
When you're in the streets, raise hell.
但当他们得到你  他们得到了你
But when they get you, they got you.
好一点
Be nice.
就这些了吗  少校  就这样
Will that be all, major? That will be all.
我们不会在这里呆那么久
We won't be here that long.
很高兴为您效劳  先生
Well, glad to be of service, sir.
埃切瓦里…
Echevarria...
我的挖沟刀
my trench knife.
我是说  你要去哪里  第二次  他们绞死你
I mean, where you going? Second time around, they hang you.
今晚不能改变  少校
Can't change overnight, major.
我也不能
Neither can I.
起飞
Take off.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
刀子  恢复
Knife! Recover!
坚持下去  孩子
Stick them, boy!
打死德国佬
Hit the kraut!
恢复
Recover!
刀子  恢复
Knife! Recover!
撞上德国佬  宝贝
Hit the kraut, baby!
-是的  恢复
- Yeah! - Recover!
很好  很好  刀子
- Good, good. - Knife!
恢复
Recover!
左边  恢复
Left! Recover!
把它们粘起来  肖蒂  -就是这样
- Stick them, Shorty! - That's it.
少校  他们从哪儿弄到你的守卫帽的
Where did they get your garrison cap, major?
我不知道  Stern
I don't know, Stern.
邪恶与邪恶  我猜
Evil versus evil, I guess.
恢复  刀子
Recover! Knife!
坚持他  肖蒂
Stick him, Shorty!
再来一次  快点  肖蒂
Stick that kraut again! Come on, Shorty!
他的名字叫莱特少校
His name is Major Wright.
这是我们仅有的一部电影
This is the only film we have.
它是在一个濒死的新闻摄影师旁边找到的
It was found next to a dying newsreel cameraman.
这部电影是在袭击阿格里真托村时拍摄的
The film was made during an attack on the village of Agrigento
其中的目标被认为是本尼托·墨索里尼
in which the target is believed to have been Benito Mussolini.
我们的新联系人说  即使现在  这个军官正在训练另一个小组
Our new contact says that even now, this officer is training another group
被判死刑的美国囚犯
drawn from American prisoners sentenced to death
或长期监禁
or long terms of imprisonment.
整个故事看起来有点不可思议  将军
The whole story seems a little incredible, general.
你确定你不是在浪费钱吗  呃  这个线人
Are you sure you're not wasting money on this, uh, this informant?
这是我们在爱尔兰的高级代理商的意见
It is the opinion of our senior agent in Ireland
这个故事是千真万确的
that the story is absolutely true.
嗯  也许你是对的
Well, maybe you're right.
整个国家崇拜歹徒和歹徒
The whole country worships outlaws and gangsters.
我想他们现在已经把他们征召入伍了
Now they've drafted them into the Army, I suppose.
我已经安排好从这个告密者那里收到更多的报告
I've made arrangements to receive further reports from this informant.
我们将提供所有必要的技术设备
And we will supply all necessary technical equipment
未来需要传输
needed for transmission in the future.
请稍等片刻
One moment, please.
帝国总理  将军
The Reich's chancellery, general.
李希特将军
General Richter.
是的  我很喜欢
Yes, mein F躧rer.
不  我不会有问题的
No, mein F躧rer, it will not be a problem.
我们将于九月三日在伊斯坦布尔
We shall be in Istanbul on September the 3rd.
是的  我很喜欢
Yes, mein F躧rer.
谢谢您
Thank you.
如果没有更多的事情  先生们…
If there is nothing further, gentlemen...
你真的相信这个人可以接受
And you honestly believe that this man can take
一群不称职的杀人犯…
a bunch of misfits, murderers...
和普通小偷
and common thieves
把他们变成一个有凝聚力的战斗机器
and turn them into a cohesive fighting machine?
哦  这不是一个完全原创的概念  先生们：
Oh, it is not an entirely original concept, gentlemen:
该死的军团
A "legion of the damned."
通常  我是第一个出去的人
Ordinarily, I'd be the first man out,
但这是我们的处女航
but since this is our maiden voyage,
Holt中士将履行这些荣誉
Sergeant Holt will do the honours.
怎么了  穆兹  你看起来有点紧张
What's the matter, Mu馿z? You seem a little tense.
我签约杀死德国人  而不是跳出飞机
I signed up to kill Germans, not jump out of planes.
错了
Wrong.
你本来是该下去的
You were due to go down one way or another.
在绳子的末端有六英尺  或者离飞机有6000英尺
Either six foot at the end of a rope, or 6000 feet from an airplane.
瞧  你自己赚了不少钱
Look, you got yourself a good deal.
我拿到好价钱后会告诉你的  少校
I'll let you know when I got a good deal, major.
现在  一般来说  你有好几天的准备时间
Now, ordinarily, you'd have several days for preparation
你的第一次跳伞是在白天进行的
and your first jump would have been in the daytime.
但是没有时间  你的下一跳现在
But there is no time. Your next jump now
将在夜间进入南斯拉夫
will be at night and into Yugoslavia.
连接你的电缆
Attach your cables.
祝你好运
Good luck.
去吧
Go!
达哥斯蒂诺
D'Agostino?
你到底怎么了  达哥斯蒂诺
What the hell's wrong with you, D'Agostino?
我不会跳  少校
I can't jump, major.
我从来就不擅长高处  我做不到
I never been any good at heights. I can't do it.
告诉某人  这是个地狱  士兵
It's a hell of a time to tell somebody, soldier!
站起来跳  不  少校
Get up there and jump! No, major.
我不能  我会被杀的  我知道
I can't. I'll get killed, I know it.
你想让每个人都知道热门的辛迪加袭击了人…
You want everybody to know that the hotshot syndicate hit man...
有一英里长的黄色条纹吗
has a yellow streak a mile long?
我不能跳  少校
I can't jump, major!
你太酷了
You're so cool.
你甚至给了他们最后一根烟
You even offered them a last drag from your own cigarette
就在你开动脑筋之前
just before you blew their brains out.
你想要香烟吗  跳  你这个流浪汉
You want a cigarette? Jump, you bum.
我得走了  我会冻住我的腿  加油  我们走吧
I got to go. I'll freeze my leg. Come on! Let's get going!
-移动或挤奶  -来吧
- Move it or milk it. - Come on.
-来吧  移动它  这里已经结冰了
- Come on, move it. - It's freezing up here.
来吧  我们走吧  杰罗尼莫
Come on, let's move! Geronimo!
要再看看欧洲  对吧  霍夫曼
Gotta be a nicer way to see Europe again, right, Hoffman?
嗨  少校  我是一个全美国男孩
Hey, major, I'm an all-American boy.
我的父母只是四处游逛
My parents just travelled around a lot.
哦  天哪
Oh, my God!
昨晚…
Last night...
霍夫曼反弹后
after Hoffman bounced
我把他的尸体带回来了  还有他的降落伞
I had his body brought back here, along with his parachute.
你认为这不仅仅是一次常规的训练事故  少校
You think this was more than a routine training accident, major?
我现在知道了  中尉  这不是意外
I know now, lieutenant, that it was no accident.
霍夫曼降落伞上的降落伞线被切断了
The chute line on Hoffman's parachute was cut.
他跳伞时跳得很好
He jumped out of that plane with the jump ring in perfect position
溜槽仍然没有打开
and the chute still didn't open.
我以为那些人装了自己的滑道
I thought the men packed their own chutes.
不  你说的是伞兵  中尉
No, you're talking about paratroopers, lieutenant.
我的人是小偷和杀人犯
My men are thieves and murderers.
这些是预先折叠  并由跳转教练在飞机上
These are prefolded and put on an airplane by jump instructors.
任何人都可以得到霍夫曼的降落伞
Anybody could have got to Hoffman's parachute,
甚至帮了他一把
even helped him on with it.
你自己说的  少校  你有小偷和杀人犯
You said it yourself, major. You've got thieves and murderers.
所以他们中的一个找到了另一个杀人的理由
So one of them found a reason to kill another.
这就是我半夜把我弄出来的原因吗
Is that a reason for getting me out here in the middle of the night?
不  我的理由是霍夫曼是我的一个男人
No. My reason is Hoffman was one of my men.
他非常重要
And he was very important.
他讲德语
He spoke German.
他在欧洲旅行多年  熟悉南斯拉夫
He travelled in Europe for years and he was familiar with Yugoslavia,
这对我有很大帮助
which would have been a great help to me.
那么你是说你需要时间去寻找替代品
So you're saying you need time to find a replacement?
没有时间了  上校  纳粹会转移那些人
There is no time, colonel. The Nazis are gonna move those people.
少校  你说霍夫曼在欧洲呆了几年
Major, you say that Hoffman spent years in Europe,
拿起语言  他知道巴尔干半岛
picking up languages, he knew the Balkans.
我在欧洲长大  我会说很多欧洲语言
I grew up in Europe. I speak many European languages
我在Balkans和南斯拉夫度过了六个夏天
and I spent six summers in the Balkans and Yugoslavia.
显然  不管出于什么原因  中尉  你想继续执行这个任务
Apparently, for whatever reason, lieutenant, you want to go on this mission.
让我给你指出点什么
Let me point something out to you.
现在  剩下的训练和敌后
Now, for the rest of the training and behind enemy lines,
你的生活将完全取决于在书中犯下一切罪行的人
your life will totally depend on men who've committed every crime in the book,
包括强奸和谋杀  现在  你还想去吗
including rape and murder. Now, do you still want to go?
嘿  萨奇  今晚有谁在看电影
Hey, sarge, who's in the movies tonight?
贝蒂·格莱伯  对吧
Betty Grable, right?
是啊  她唱着歌跳进你的心里
Yeah, singing and dancing her way into your heart.
来吧  让我们摆脱寒冷
Come on, let's get out of the cold.
在霍夫曼弹跳后  少校为什么要起飞
How come the major took off with Hoffman's chute after he bounced?
我与专业相处的方式
The way I get along with the major
每当我有一个大的  肥胖的问题给他…
is whenever I have a big, fat question for him...
我完全忘记了这件事
I forget all about it.
嘿  看  这儿有个女的
Hey, look, there's a dame in here!
-好吧  把它关掉  把它关掉
- All right, knock it off! - Knock it off.
找个座位坐在上面
Find yourselves a seat and sit on it.
-我们见过面  不是吗  她很漂亮
- We've met, haven't we? - She's beautiful.
这是Lieutenant Campbell
This is Lieutenant Campbell.
她会和我们一起参加剩下的训练
She'll be with us for the rest of the training
她也会和我们一起跳到欧洲
and she'll also jump with us into Europe.
好的  记住…
All right, keep in mind...
她是个军官
that she's an officer
她给出的任何命令
and any order she gives
将立即服从  明白了吗
will be obeyed immediately. Is that clear?
是的  先生
Yes, sir!
即使她想利用我们  先生
Even if she wants to take advantage of us, sir?
好的  中士  按一下开关
All right, sergeant, hit the switch.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
名字  克兰兹  沃尔夫冈
Name? Kranz, Wolfgang.
对党的重要性  社会规划师和管理员
Importance to the party? Social planner and administrator.
在达豪和贝尔森建立了营地
Created the camps at Dachau and Belsen.
很好  Stern
Very good, Stern.
名字  Ulrich Brunner  中尉
Name? Ulrich Brunner. Lieutenant.
对党的重要性
Importance to the party?
某种银行家  不是吗
Some kind of banker, isn't he?
是的  有原则的年轻金融顾问
Yes, a principled young financial adviser
给Reichminister  阿尔贝特·施佩尔
to the Reichminister, Albert Speer.
钢铁  赫尔穆特…
Steel, Helmut...
体育先知
physical culture prophet.
指导性革命计划
Directs a sexual revolutionary program
据说是为了让所有年轻女人怀孕
supposedly aimed at impregnating all young women
在整个帝国
throughout the Greater Reich.
是啊  你觉得这个人怎么样  中尉
Yeah? How do you like this guy, lieutenant?
我想我们必须缩短他的职业生涯
I think we'll have to cut his career short.
现在  记住那些面孔
Now, remember those faces.
他们不会总是穿礼服制服和十字花剑臂章
They won't always be wearing dress uniforms and swastika armbands.
他们可能穿着便服  或者装扮成医务工作者
They may be in civilian clothes, or dressed as medical workers
或正统教士
or orthodox priests.
嗨  少校  怎么会是12  假设我们只给你10或11
Hey, major, how come it has to be 12? Suppose we only get you 10 or 11?
-是的  为什么不呢  -不好
- Yeah, why not? - No good.
坐在那列火车上的那个
That one that's left on that train
可能是阿道夫·希特勒的继承人  下一个继承人
may be the heir apparent to Adolf Hitler, the next f黨rer.
击中开关  警官
Hit the switch, sergeant.
接下来是一部关于占领南斯拉夫的德国电影
The next is a captured German film on the occupation of Yugoslavia.
你会注意到所有的…
You'll notice that all the...
我从来没见过这样的驻军
I ain't never seen no garrison like this.
我也一样
Me neither.
哇
Whoa.
现在到底是谁把一部蓝色电影偷偷带进了最高安全监狱
Now who the hell smuggled a blue film into a maximum-security prison?
埃切瓦里
Echevarria?
少校  我跟这事没关系
Major, I had nothing to do with this.
这是一个废话  不  当然不是
It's a bum rap. No, of course not.
我相信我已经修过这门课了
I believe I've already had this course in training.
如果你需要我  我就在外面
I'll be outside if you need me.
你会错过最好的部分
You're gonna miss the best part.
先生  要不要让它继续  是啊
Shall I let it continue, sir? Yeah...
不妨看看另一半的生活
might as well see how the other half lives.
我喜欢这个  我喜欢
I like that, I like that.
我从食堂里拿出来的
I got this out of the mess hall.
警卫有45码和机关枪
The guards have got.45s and machine guns.
你忘了吗  我们先拿到专业
Did you forget about that? We'll get the major first.
他有45卡宾枪  弹药很多
He's got a.45 carbine, lots of ammo.
然后我们在营房找到警卫  我们得到他的酒吧
Then we get the guard at the barracks and we get his BAR.
我们抓起一辆卡车  我们把所有的车都停住了
We grab one of the trucks and we disable all the others.
我们从这里去哪里  西海岸  爱尔兰中立
Where do we go from here? West coast. Ireland's neutral.
我们抓住一艘船  我们到达爱尔兰  我们拉几个工作  得到一个赌注
We grab a boat, we get to Ireland, we pull a few jobs, get a stake.
嘿  真是个好主意  你疯了吗
Hey, that's a great idea. Are you crazy?
你说得对  这是个馊主意
You're right. It's a lousy idea.
谁主修专业
Who sticks the major?
我以为你会这么做的  达哥斯蒂诺
I thought you'd do that, D'Agostino.
他把你踢出了飞机
He kicked you out of the plane.
把刀子给我
Give me the knife.
你疯了吗  你会让我们三个人都被杀
Are you nuts? You'll get all three of us killed
然后把其他十字架钉死  那么你来这里干什么
and then crucify the others too. What did you come out here for, then?
因为你问过我们
Because you asked us.
我们想看看有多少人疯了
And we wanted to see how many other men were crazy.
是的  没错  我们没那么疯狂
Yeah, that's right. We ain't that crazy.
容易的  轻松点  肖蒂  容易的
Easy. Easy, Shorty. Easy!
容易的  嘿  很容易
Easy. Hey, easy.
你还好吗  你没事吧
You okay? Are you okay?
是的  我没事
Yeah, I'm all right.
嘿  这些家伙不好
Hey, these guys ain't nice.
嘿  现在  回到你的床铺…
Hey. Now, go on back to your bunks...
不要再有任何聪明的想法
and don't get any more bright ideas.
晚安  少校
Good night, major.
走的路  冠军
Way to go, champ.
走吧  伙计  好的
Way to go, buddy. All right.
现在  只要记住  如果这是真的
Now, just remember, if this was the real thing
你移动得太快了  你会被工程师发现的…
and you move too soon, you'd be spotted by the engineers...
或者德国乘客在车内
or the German passengers inside the cars.
他们会把火车停下来  把我们铲起来
They'd stop the train and just scoop us up
我们永远也不会接近任何我们想要接近的人
and we'd never get near anybody we want to get on it.
采取立场
Take positions.
根据数字  一个…
By the numbers. One...
二  三  四…
two, three, four...
五  六…
five, six...
七…
seven...
八  九  10, 11, 12
eight, nine, 10, 11, 12.
-好的  搬回去
- All right. - Moving back.
这里谁负责  好吧  掉下来
Who's in charge here? All right, fall out.
卡车在哪里
Where the hell's the truck?
看  少校来了
Look, here comes the major.
好吧  你干得不错
All right, you did a good job.
我对你的工作相当满意
And I'm reasonably happy with your work.
这辆卡车在这里  一半是酒
This truck here, it's half full of booze.
掉下来
Fall out.
好的  Collins  埃切瓦里…
All right. Collins, Echevarria...
放下后门
drop the tailgate.
小心货物
And careful with the cargo.
嘿  就这样  宝贝
Hey, that's it, baby.
我想你可以处理所有这些
I assume you can handle all of that.
现在  姑娘们  你们的首相期待着
Now, girls, your prime minister is looking forward
来装饰你们每一个人
to decorating each and every one of you individually.
好的  快点吧
Okay, so hurry it up.
好看  很好
Good-looking. Good.
给我一个  -你走吧
- Give me one. - Here you go.
我叫Lonnie
My name's Lonnie.
我知道该带你去哪儿  小心
I know where to take you. Be careful.
嘿  看着它
Hey, watch it.
你把袜子带来尼龙
You brought stockings in nylon?
- Baby  这是另外一个
- Baby. - Here's another one.
弗雷迪
Freddie!
我找到了你  亲爱的  你看起来很棒
I've found you, love. You look great.
给我们一个吻
Give us a kiss.
那么你像我们的突击队员吗
Are you something like our commandos, then?
早上告诉我  宝贝  好吗
Tell me about it in the morning, baby, okay?
宝贝  我从晚上开始就没跳舞了  来吧
Baby, I haven't danced since grad night. Come on.
是的  就是这样  我简直不敢相信
- Yeah, that's it. - I can't believe it!
我们还没有正式介绍
We haven't been formally introduced yet.
胭脂红
Carmine D'Agostino.
好了  中尉  少校似乎有
Well, lieutenant, the major appears to have
某种不同寻常的夜间演习正在进行中
some kind of unusual night manoeuvre in progress.
是的  先生  我相信他把它称为
Yes, sir. I believe he referred to it as
改善与盟国的关系
"improving relations with our allies."
的确
Indeed.
上校  好吧  我没想到会在野外看到你
Colonel. Well, I didn't expect to see you out in the field, so to speak.
我看得出来  不用了  谢谢
I can see that. No, thank you.
你意识到这个小小的狂欢会让你受到法庭审判
You realize this little orgy could get you court-martialled.
这些被判犯有死刑罪的囚犯
These are sentenced prisoners convicted of capital crimes.
他们也准备战斗了  上校  来吧  让他们休息一下
They're also ready for battle, colonel. Come on, give them a break.
少校  如果你能忍耐撕裂自己
Major, if you could bear to tear yourself away,
将军正在路上等你
the general is waiting for you down the road.
哦  他想参加聚会吗
Oh, did he want to join the party?
Collins
Collins.
运气好  士兵
Get lucky, soldier.
你要见我  少校  我有个问题  先生
You wanted to see me, major? I've got a problem, sir.
我们有好几个  我们有两份报告
We have several. We have two reports.
一个来自南斯拉夫内部
One from inside Yugoslavia
表明在所有主要城市突然增加了安全性
indicating suddenly increased security in all the major cities.
嗯  你选择南斯拉夫是因为它在主要东方快车路线上
Well, you picked Yugoslavia because it's on the main Orient Express route.
这是正确的  游击队在等你
That's right. And the partisans are expecting you.
但第二次报道
But the second report
是纳粹开始了解你自己以及你的所作所为
is that the Nazis are beginning to learn about you personally and what you do.
嗯  我并不感到惊讶
Well, I'm not surprised.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
将军  我在这里问过你  因为我相信我们组有叛徒
General, I asked you here because I believe there's a traitor in our group.
你知道他是谁吗  不  还没有
Do you know who he is? No, not yet.
但他得到了霍夫曼的降落伞
But he got to Hoffman's parachute
他在南斯拉夫对我来说是无价之宝
and he would have been invaluable to me in Yugoslavia.
我浏览了文件夹
I went through the folders.
霍夫曼根本不可能遇到这些人
And there's no way that Hoffman could've met any of these men
在来到军事监狱之前
before coming to the military prison.
不  德国人下令杀戮
No, the Germans ordered the killing.
但是纳粹怎么可能知道你要挑选谁来完成这项任务呢
But how could the Nazis possibly have known who you were going to pick for the mission?
他们不能  很明显  我们的Somebody先生
They couldn't. Obviously, our Mr. Somebody,
我派他去执行任务后  他和德国人取得了联系
he got in touch with the Germans after I assigned him to the mission.
你知道有一部蓝色电影偷偷进入营地吗
You know there was a blue film smuggled into the camp?
如果你能在……走私一部蓝色电影
And if you can smuggle a blue film in...
你当然可以把信息偷运出去
you certainly can smuggle a message out.
然后我们必须中止任务
Then we have to abort the mission.
我们该怎么做  克拉克
How do we do that, Clark?
第三帝国的继承人今晚离开慕尼黑
The heirs apparent to the Third Reich leave Munich tonight.
他们将在三天内到达伊斯坦布尔
They'll arrive in Istanbul in three days.
那是一个聚会
That's some party.
你为什么不加入我们呢
Why don't you join us?
如果我参加那个聚会  恐怕我会失去我的酒吧
If I joined that party, I'm afraid I'd lose my bars.
Lieutenant Campbell  你当军官多久了
How long have you been an officer, Lieutenant Campbell?
五个月
Five months.
我得到了直接的佣金
I was given a direct commission
因为我有一定的技能和教育…
because I have certain skills and education...
在上面和上面需要什么
over and above what's needed there.
你就像其他肮脏的人一样
You're just like the rest of the Dirty Dozen.
是啊  我们都有一定的技能
Yeah. We all got certain skills
还有教育
and education too.
你知道什么是讽刺吗
You know what's ironic?
那些人犯了罪  他们被关进监狱…
Those men committed crimes, they were put in prison...
他们完成了这个任务
and they got this mission.
我会愿意付出我所拥有的一切
I would've been willing to give everything I have.
也许是我的生活
Maybe my life.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不  不要停下来
No. Don't stop now.
爸爸是一名外国服务人员
By dad is a Foreign Service officer.
他在奥斯陆驻扎时娶了一位挪威妇女
He married a Norwegian woman when he was stationed in Oslo.
纳粹袭击挪威的时候
When the Nazis hit Norway,
我母亲回家把家人带出去了
my mother had gone home to get her family out.
她在第一次轰炸中丧生
She died in the first bombing raid.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
现在  我们可以尝试在空旷的火车上进行空袭
Now, we can try an air strike at the train in open country,
但我们不能肯定他们会得到12个
but we can't be sure they'd get all 12.
然后  我们可以把它交给亚历山大市的英国情报部门
And then, we could give this to British intelligence at Alexandria.
嘿  等一下  我的人呢
Hey, wait a minute. How about my men?
我的意思是  他们一直在努力工作  他们准备出发了
I mean, they've been working damn hard and they're ready to go!
我的工作人员是对的  你真的成了他们中的一员
My staff is right. You really do become one of them.
他们必须回到监狱  现在等一下  将军
They'd have to go back to prison. Now wait a minute, general.
如果你把这些人送回去死
If you send these men back to do time and die,
你的手上会发生骚乱
you're gonna have a riot on your hands.
也许你是对的  我可能会站在他们一边
And you may be right. I might be fighting on their side.
你到底要什么  少校  你有一个叛徒在你的小组  你不知道是谁
What the hell do you want, major? You've got a traitor in your group and you don't know who it is.
我不知道是谁  但在某个地方
I don't know who it is, but somewhere down the line
我会查出是谁  然后除掉他
I'll find out who it is and get rid of him.
除了炸毁纳粹或死亡尝试
Besides blowing up the Nazis or die trying.
这是游戏的名称  当谈到肮脏的打
And that's the name of the game when it comes to the Dirty Dozen.
除了喝酒和嫖妓…
Besides drinking and whoring...
摔倒了
and falling down.
其中一个是叛徒
And one of them is a traitor.
我们正在接近跳跃区  少校
We're approaching the jump area, major.
我们随时都会打开准备好的灯
We'll be turning on the ready light at any moment.
让我们看看
Let's see.
坐标4135-1792  对吗
Coordinates 4135-2794, is that right?
当然可以  先生  有什么问题吗
Well, of course, sir. Any problem?
不  不  不  没问题  除非我们不跳
No, no, no. No problem. Except we're not gonna jump there.
是的  我想让你改变斯科普里南部5度
Yes, I want you to change course 5 degrees south of Skopje
绕过跳跃区域约20英里  你明白了吗
and bypass the jump area by some 20 miles. Have you got that?
先生  这一切都很不规则  你在破坏计划
This is all very irregular, sir. You're breaking the plan.
嗯  我的整个团队都是不规则的  先生们  这是他们工作的一部分
Well, my whole group is irregular, gentlemen. That's part of their job.
我们必须向我们的C.O报告
We'll have to report it to our C.O.
我不在乎你做了多少报告  上尉
I don't care how many reports you make, captain,
只要新的坐标是4131-2595  你明白了吗
just as long as the new coordinates are 4131-2795. Have you got that?
嘿  这到底是怎么回事
Hey, what the hell's going on here?
我们正在改变方向
We're changing directions.
少校  如果我们不跳到我们计划的地方
Major, if we don't jump where we planned,
我们将如何与抵抗联系起来
how will we link up with the Resistance?
你让我担心
You let me worry about that.
我在斯科普里有一个地址
I've got an address in Skopje.
你和我会找到它的  Demchuk
You and I will find it, Demchuk.
Vasco  他们要迟到了
They are running late, Vasco.
他们会来的  我姐姐收到…
They'll be here. My sister received...
出了问题  我得回斯科普里了
Something's gone wrong. I have to get back to Skopje.
无论如何我们都得离开这里
We have to get out of here in any case.
无论发生什么事  我都需要一个囚犯来审讯
Whatever happens, I need one prisoner for interrogation.
我们要那六个
We'll take those six.
你们这些人  投降
You men, surrender!
我有你的囚犯审问  上尉
I have your prisoner for interrogation, captain.
让他活着
Keep him alive.
先生  请不要往下看
Don't look down, sir.
看着他们就好像你恨他们一样
Look at them as if you hate them
他们肯定你是南斯拉夫人
and they will be sure you are Yugoslav.
对  阿瑞斯是战争之神
Yes? Ares is the god of war.
我们都是他的孩子
And we are all his children.
进来
Come in.
站住  拿起他们的枪
Stand still. Take their guns.
这到底是什么
Now, what the hell is this?
保持安静  彼得  检查一下弹药
Keep quiet. Peter, check the ammunition.
美国陆军  标准问题
U.S. Army, standard issue,
45口径弹药  全新的
.45-calibre ammunition, brand-new.
你在找谁  我已经给过你密码了
Who are you looking for? I already gave you the password.
密码可能已经被那些被撕掉舌头的人折磨掉了
The password could have been tortured out of men who then had their tongues torn out.
你在找谁  党派领袖
Who are you looking for? A partisan leader.
缩写Y.V.
Initials Y.V.
我是Yelena Vascovic
I am Yelena Vascovic.
没有人知道你只有我的姓名首字母
No one else knew that you had only my initials.
昨晚发生了什么事
What happened last night?
嘿  看  我可以说得好些  没有那个炮指着我的头
Hey, look, I can talk a lot better without that cannon pointing at my head.
对不起  对不起
Please, I'm sorry.
我理解
I understand.
我命令着陆区上空飞行
I ordered an overflight over the landing area.
我只是预感到德国人在那里等着我们
I just had a hunch that maybe the Germans were there waiting for us.
没有党派会把你交给德国人
No partisan would give you to the Germans.
嘿  我没那么说
Hey, I didn't say that.
好吧  我们接到命令  不管什么原因  我们没有联系
Okay, we had orders that, for whatever reason we didn't make any contact,
我们是来这里的  我们到了
we were to come here. So here we are.
那些想见你的人没有回来
The men that were supposed to meet you did not come back.
我们整晚都没听到他们说的话
We have heard no word all night from them.
最好假设他们被带走了
It's best to assume they were taken.
其中一个是我弟弟
One of them was my brother.
如果他们幸运的话  他们就有机会战斗了
If they were lucky, they had a chance to fight.
看  我们能给海岸附近的英国潜艇发个口信吗
Look, can we get a message to the British submarine off the coast?
是的  当然  告诉他们我们成功了
Yes, of course. Tell them we made it.
鹰四狮一  鹰四狮一
Eagle Four to Lion One. Eagle Four to Lion One.
你能读懂我吗
Can you read me?
是的  这是狮子一号  请往前走
- Yes, this is Lion One. - Go ahead, please.
这是老鹰四号  718-9.
This is Eagle Four. 7-187-9.
192724.
来访者已经到了
The visitors have arrived.
很好  我有一个来自伦敦霸王的信息
Very good. I have a message from Overlord in London.
你能马上离开SK Opje吗
Can you get out of Sk opje at once?
他们必须对你决定着陆地点的反应做出反应
They must be reacting to your decision to overfly the landing site.
告诉我出了什么事
Tell me what's wrong.
没什么不对的  我们正在路上
Nothing's wrong. We're on our way.
肯定的
Affirmative.
很好  再见
Very good. Cheerio.
对不起  昨晚你弟弟来接我们
Look, I'm sorry your brother came to meet us last night.
我的哥哥  上帝愿意  已经死了
My brother, God willing, is dead.
他又失去知觉了
He's lost consciousness again.
是的  我能看到
Yes, I can see that.
我让你查明Major Wright要袭击火车
I asked you to find out where Major Wright will attack the train
经过数小时的审讯  你没有结果
and after hours of interrogation, you have no results.
将军  请原谅我  但最好还是把火车挂起来
Forgive me, general. But would it not be better to hold up the train
还是走另一条路
or take another route?
我应该给F解释什么
What explanation am I supposed to give the f黨rer?
我不能把他的部下从叛徒专业中解救出来
That I cannot save his men from a renegade major
还有12个普通罪犯
and 12 common criminals?
你想去那列火车吗
Where do you want to hit that train?
这是我们穿越空旷国家的计划…
This is the plan We go through open country...
我们在附近的火车上相遇
and we meet the train here, near Nish.
在保加利亚边境以北20英里处有一个立交桥
There's an overpass about 20 miles north of the Bulgarian border,
在Pirot附近
near Pirot.
火车因等级下降而减慢速度
The train slows down there because of a grade.
我训练了我的男人
And I've trained my men
从立交桥上跳上这些移动的汽车
to jump on these moving cars from the overpass
把这些纳粹分子赶走
to take out these Nazi hotshots.
然后我会向我的人解释  如果他们有什么问题  我会告诉你的
Then I'll explain it to my men. If they have any problems, I'll let you know.
Stern  我能为你做点什么
Well, what can I do for you, Stern?
少校  有点糊涂了
The men are a little confused, major.
哦  也许有点害怕吧
Oh, a little scared, maybe?
嗯  很多事情都没有发生
Well, a lot of things have been happening that don't quite add up.
首先  霍夫曼从那架飞机上跳了出来
First, Hoffman jumps out of that plane and bounces.
霍夫曼在一次训练事故中丧生
Hoffman was killed in a training accident.
只有你抓住了尸体和溜槽  才把他救出来
Only you grabbed the body and the chute and got him out of there.
是的  那么我们不应该跳到我们应该去的地方
Yeah, then we don't jump where we're supposed to,
我们不进入斯科普里  我们在山上蜿蜒
we don't go into Skopje, we wind up in the hills.
如果你想和德国人一起跳下去在斯科普里散步
If you wanted to jump down with the Germans and walk in Skopje,
你是我的客人  乔
you be my guest, Joe.
怎么回事  少校
What the hell's going on, major?
好的  你有权知道
All right. You're entitled to know.
这次肮脏的打电话响了
There's a ringer in the Dirty Dozen this time.
是的  腐烂了
That's right, something rotten.
一个把我们都卖掉的犹大
A Judas who's selling us all out.
难道它不是南斯拉夫人吗
Couldn't it be one of the Yugoslavians?
不  南斯拉夫人没有切开霍夫曼的斜线
No, the Yugoslavs didn't slice Hoffman's chute line.
这是我们的一个  离家乡很近
It's one of us, closer to home.
对
Yes?
贝尔格莱德  将军
Belgrade, general.
李希特将军
General Richter.
给我坐标
Give me the coordinates.
立即通知柏林奥伯曼曼多
Notify Oberkommando Berlin immediately.
不  没关系  我自己打电话
No, never mind, I will make the call myself.
他们不到一小时前就在这里进攻了
They attacked here less than an hour ago.
但是  先生  我们的信息是  他们将继续使用
But, sir, our information was that they would go on to Nish.
这是正确的
That's right.
少校莱特没有降落伞  我们预期他
Major Wright did not parachute in where we expected him.
他没有攻击我们所期望的他
He didn't attack where we expected him.
我怀疑他是否会攻击我们所期望的火车
I doubt very much if he'll attack the train where we expect him.
让飞机15分钟后起飞
Get a plane ready to leave in 15 minutes.
为Sofia提供航班信息
File flight information for Sofia.
他死了  长官  是的  我能看见  上尉
He's dead, sir. Yes, I can see that, captain.
我以为我们要穿越空旷的国家
I thought we were going through open country.
我猜少校一直在改变主意
The major keeps changing his mind, I guess.
你知道我在想什么吗  我不知道
You know what I been thinking? I got no idea.
我以前从未有过中尉
I never had a lieutenant before.
你今天要把尸体带到Pirot埋葬和归还吗
You're taking the body to Pirot for burial and returning today?
是死者的遗愿
Was last wish of deceased.
你的试卷看起来很整齐  等一下
Your papers seem to be in order. Wait a minute.
你来自哪个村庄
What village are you from?
库马诺沃  先生  离这儿只有几英里远
Kumanovo, sir. Just few miles from here.
我知道那个该死的村庄在哪里
I know where the damn village is.
有多少游击队员藏匿在那里  等待杀害德国士兵
How many partisans are hiding there, waiting to murder German soldiers?
没有  长官  我知道
None, sir, that I know of.
说谎
Lying.
该死的马其顿人
Damned Macedonians.
在哀悼中  你呢
In mourning, are you?
亲爱的死去的灵魂  是的
For a dear departed soul, yes.
你几乎可以是德国人了
You could almost be German.
北欧  嗯  纯的
Nordic, hm? Pure.
纯在这个国家的猪
Pure in this country of swine.
打开棺材
Open the coffin.
我想看看你是否在边境走私任何东西…
I want to see if you're smuggling anything across the border...
除了死者
besides the dead.
长官  神圣服务结束了
Sir, it was closed after holy service.
在这一生中  有…然后我会打开它
In this life, there is... Then I will open it.
是啊
Yeah?
好吧  里面一定有电话
All right, there must be a phone in there.
贝尔格莱德正试图回击  他们一定过去了
Belgrade is trying to call back. They must have got through.
好的  五分钟后我们就离开这里
All right, we'll be out of here in five minutes.
半小时后天就黑了
And it'll be dark in a half-hour.
正规军一路  对吗  中士
Regular Army all the way, right, sergeant?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
看  我得到了穆兹的狗标签
Look, I got Mu馿z's dog tags.
如果有什么事情发生在我身上…
If anything should happen to me...
我希望你能把这些标签拿回来  如果可以的话
I want you to get those tags back, if you can.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
现在  我们应该袭击边境上的火车
Now, we're supposed to attack the train on the border.
真正的目标  Sofia以东
The real target? East of Sofia.
所以我在学校的最后一年
So my last year in school,
我要么结婚  要么尝试外国服务
I was either gonna get married or try for the Foreign Service.
一定是一个艰难的决定
Must have been a hell of a tough decision.
不要笑  我可能是个很好的妻子…
Don't laugh. I might have been a very good wife...
安德鲁是一位相当聪明的外国服务官员
andlor a reasonably bright Foreign Service officer.
可能是  你还不能吗
Might have been? Can't you still be?
我认为未来不远  乔
I don't think that far ahead in the future, Joe.
不再了
Not anymore.
你呢  没有战后的计划
What about you? No postwar plans?
我在战争中已经很久了
I've been in the war a long time.
没有别的路可走吗
No other way to go?
不
No.
反正我也不知道
I don't know of one, anyway.
嗯  这不是完全正确的
Well, that's not altogether true.
只是有时候…
It's just that sometimes...
我想给全世界每一个犹太人一个自动武器  并说：
I want to give every Jew in the world an automatic weapon and say:
抓住这一点  在这个世纪  你需要它来活下去
"Hold onto this, you're gonna need it just to stay alive in this century."
有时候我想    天哪  肯定有时间……
And other times I think, " My God, there must be some time..."
当我不需要为了活着而杀戮
when I don't have to kill just to stay alive."
-早上好  先生们  -早上好
- Good morning, gentlemen. - Good morning.
上校  最近有什么事
What's the latest, colonel?
我们有一份来自贝尔格莱德的地下报告
We have an underground report from Belgrade.
昨晚火车上没有发生任何袭击
There was no attack on the train last night
一小时前  他们跨进了保加利亚
and they crossed into Bulgaria roughly an hour ago.
亚得里亚海的英国潜艇部队呢
What about the English Submarine Force out here in the Adriatic?
自从上一次斯科普里通讯以来  没有任何消息
No word since the last communication from Skopje.
假设德国人占领了公寓
The assumption is the Germans have seized the apartment
摧毁了通信设备
and destroyed the communications equipment.
嗯  也许他只是害怕使用它  直到他发现谁站在他一边
Well, maybe he's just afraid to use it until he finds out who's on his side.
将军  火车是从土耳其边境出发的半天路程
General, that train is one half day's journey from the Turkish border.
穿越边境的那一刻
The moment it crosses the border
对它的任何攻击都是对土耳其的战争行为
any attack upon it is an act of war on Turkey.
你到底想从我这里得到什么  克拉克
What the hell do you want from me, Clark?
我相信莱特会进攻的
I'm sure Wright will attack
当他看到有机会成功的时候
when he sees there's some chance to succeed.
将军  我已经自由了
General, I've taken the liberty
警告亚历山大市的第十二战斗机司令部
of alerting the 12th Fighter Command at Alexandria.
但我想我们排除了飞机
But I thought we ruled out planes
因为我们不能确定
because we couldn't be sure
从空中撞到一辆车厢里的12个人
of hitting 12 men in one railroad car from the air.
你有估计吗
You have an estimate?
他们可以在今天的1200个小时里抢火车
They could scramble and attack the train at 1200 hours today
当它还在保加利亚的时候
whilst it's still in Bulgaria,
有很好的成功机会
with a very good chance of complete success.
如果第十二战斗机群攻击
And if the 12th Fighter group attacks
同时  少校和他的人民也一样
the same time that the major and his people do,
我们不必担心德国人杀死所有肮脏的人
we won't have to worry about the Germans killing off all the Dirty Dozen.
我们会自己炸掉的
We'll blow them up ourselves.
如果这种情况发生  那就是战争  这是无济于事的
If that happens, it's war and it can't be helped.
你知道  克拉克  你是个很好的军官…
You know, Clark, you're a hell of a good officer...
但你是个私生子
but you are a bastard.
现在  他们能从亚历山大市进入的最后时刻是什么
Now, what's the last moment they can go in from Alexandria?
0900小时  先生  我们等一下
0900 hours, sir. We'll wait.
将军  现在有任何延误…我说  我们等一下
General, any delay now... I said, we'll wait.
在0900小时  如果我们没有收到他的信…
At 0900 hours, if we haven't heard from him...
莱特少校和他的指挥官将被视为行动失败
Major Wright and his command will be considered lost in action.
我们将采取另一种解决方案
And we'll go to an alternative solution.
霍尔特中士对你再次改变计划感到惊讶
Sergeant Holt seemed surprised that you changed the plans again.
是的  有些不同于男人的期望  对吧
Yes, something different from what the men expected, right?
从你第一次来到我的公寓
From the first moment you came to my apartment,
我知道出了什么事
I knew that something was wrong.
我的人也要死了
My men are dying too.
你不是时候告诉我更多了吗
Isn't it time that you tell me more?
我该告诉你我给我的人的所有信息了
It's time I told you that all the information I give to my men
被传给德国人
is transmitted right to the Germans,
可能是由一个大功率微型发射器
probably by a high-powered mini-transmitter.
那么  你必须找到叛徒然后杀了他
Well, then you have to find the traitor and kill him.
不  我必须非常小心
No, I gotta be very careful.
如果我现在太多地动摇这些人  他们可能会盲目地互相攻击
If I shake up the men too much now, they could turn on each other blindly.
不  他会走错路  我会把他钉死的
No, he'll make a wrong move and I'll nail him.
上帝帮助我们
God help us.
你的论文
Your papers?
你以前从没见过桥  是吧
You've never seen a bridge before, huh?
哦  对不起  先生  他几乎从不离开农场
Oh, sorry, sir. He almost never leaves the farm.
你有证件吗  笨蛋
You have any papers, dummy?
他给你带来不好的时间
He was giving you a bad time?
好吧  你可以这么说
Well, you could say that.
移动它
Move it!
早上好  先生们
Good morning, gentlemen.
正如你所知  我们在土耳其边境的几个小时之内
As you know, we are within a few hours of the Turkish border
在我们尊敬的轴心国  保加利亚
and within the confines of our esteemed Axis ally, Bulgaria.
将军  你愿意和我们一起去旅行吗
Will you be joining us for the rest of the trip, general?
我很遗憾我还有最后一个任务要处理
I regret I have one last mission to attend to.
但是今晚我会在伊斯坦布尔见到你们
But I shall see you all in Istanbul tonight.
让我给你留下继续安全的需要
Let me impress upon you the need for continued security.
但我向你保证
But I assure you,
f r r的命令将得到满足
the f黨rer's commands will be fulfilled.
说到F·R的命令  李希特将军
Speaking of the f黨rer's commands, General Richter,
我这儿有一封在慕尼黑寄来的信
I have here a letter delivered to me in Munich,
阿道夫·希特勒三天前在柏林签下的
signed by Adolf Hitler in Berlin three days ago.
我之前没有提到过的原因
The reason I have not mentioned it before
是因为我觉得我们仍然处于严重的危险之中
is because I felt we were still in grave danger.
安全是必不可少的
Security is essential.
先生们
Gentlemen,
千年帝国在我们手中……
the Thousand-Year Reich is in our hands...
在火车车厢2420
in train car 2420.
我向所有参与的人表达我衷心的祝愿
"I send my heartfelt good wishes to all those involved"
在这个伟大而需要的企业中
in this great and needed enterprise.
我向那些传播大德种子的人致敬
I salute those who will spread the seeds of greater Germany
遍及全世界
throughout the world.
无论发生在我身上
Whatever happens to me,
我们最后的胜利仍然是不可避免的
our final victory remains inevitable.
因此  我现在指定为我的继任者
Accordingly, I now designate as my successor
作为第四帝国的领袖…
and as the leader of the Fourth Reich...
德国空军少将
Major General of the Waffen S. S...
卡尔·李希特
"Karl Richter."
签署
Signed...
阿道夫·希特勒
Adolf Hitler.
到底发生了什么事
What the hell is going on?
彼得
Peter!
警官  我们来了
We're coming through, sergeant.
我们遇到了敌人  长官
We have met the enemy, sir.
他们走了
They are gone.
干得好
Good job.
该死的好工作
Damn good job.
好吧  让我们看看我们得到了什么
All right, let's see what we got.
那里肯定有十来个
Must be almost a full dozen of them there.
你怎么认为
What do you think?
你知道任务
You know the mission.
别开枪  我们投降
Don't shoot! We surrender.
抓住它  我们在俘虏
Hold it. We're taking prisoners.
我们可能以后需要它们
We may need them later.
是那些杂种开始了这一切
Those are the bastards who started all this.
这是命令  Stern
That's an order, Stern.
扔掉你的武器
Throw out your weapons.
你能行  少校
You can do it, major.
别让我们失望
Don't let us down.
大多数炙手可热的纳粹分子都在那里  Dravko
Most of the hotshot high-ranking Nazis are back there, Dravko.
可能是我们回家的机票
Could be our ticket home.
我不明白  我们可以去哪里
I don't understand. Where can we go?
坎贝尔中尉和我  我们在地图上发现了一条支线
Lieutenant Campbell and I, we found a spur line on the map
就到爱琴海  穿过希腊的尖端
right down to the Aegean. Cutting through the tip of Greece.
Yelena将联系英国在该地区的子公司
Yelena will contact the British sub in the area.
谁知道呢  前面一百英里  我们可能赶上
Who knows? A hundred miles ahead, and we might make it.
嘿  Demchuk
Hey, Demchuk.
少校在哪里  他正在检查那辆车
Where's the major? He's checking out that car.
我最好掩护他
I better cover him.
决定去另一边好吗  达哥斯蒂诺
Decide to go to the other side for good, D'Agostino?
我能说什么  少校  你是怎么猜到的
What can I say, major? How did you guess?
无话可说  无事可做
Nothing to say and nothing to do.
但我很好奇
But I'm curious.
当Wilson决定逃跑时
When Wilson decided to escape
你假装站在他旁边  为什么
you pretended to side with him. Why?
他在谈论爱尔兰
He was talking about Ireland.
我已经和德国领事馆谈过了
I was already talking to the German consulate there.
所以你会杀了他们三个  把他们的头给我
So you would've killed the three of them, brought me their heads.
如果必须的话
If it got to be necessary.
我不得不交付整个团队
I had to deliver the whole group.
只有Collins救了我的麻烦
Only Collins saved me the trouble.
所以你害怕从飞机上跳出来的戏剧性事件
So the high drama about you being afraid to jump out of the airplane,
只是为了掩盖你切开霍夫曼的斜道的事实  对吧
it was just to cover up the fact that you sliced Hoffman's chute, right?
少校  我从小在一个15层楼的窗子里长大
Major, I grew up hanging out the window of a 15-floor tenement.
别告诉我你是土生土长的法西斯主义者  卡迈恩
Now, don't tell me you're a native-born fascist, Carmine.
你这么做是为了钱  对吧
You did it for the money, right?
嗨  少校
Hey, major.
钱
Money.
很多钱
Lots of money.
这就是世界运转的原因
That's what makes the world go round.
见鬼去吧
See you in hell.
正确的
Right.
-来吧  把你的背放进去
- Come on. - Get your back into it!
移动它
Move it!
加油
Come on!
这是正确的
That's right.
住手  坚持住  把它举起来
Stop! Hold on, hold it up.
举起手来
Hold it up!
把它拿回来  我们可能需要那一罐汽油
Bring it back. We might need that tankful of gas.
你是说  把它放在我们面前
You mean, leave it in front of us?
把它连接起来  我们会把它一路推到希腊
Couple it on and we'll push it all the way to Greece.
好的  好吧
All right. All right!
走吧  来吧  移动它
Let's go! Come on, move it!
当火车向南行驶时  立即开始飞越
Begin immediate overflights of the train as it moves south.
但他们肯定不能乘火车到土耳其边境  长官
But surely they cannot take the train to the Turkish border, sir.
我们先去找火车  上尉
Let's find the train first, captain.
然后我们将确切地确定它的去向
Then we shall decide exactly where it's going.
请确保此刻飞机上没有一架飞机着火
Make sure that none of the planes fire on the train at this moment.
但是他们还能阻止他们吗
But how else can they stop them?
我会阻止他们的
I'll stop them.
我们不知道我们有多少人还活着
We don't know how many of our people are still alive.
作为人质  他们对这个少校莱特有巨大的价值
They have tremendous value to this Major Wright, as hostages.
他会意识到这一点的
He will be aware of that.
鹰四狮一  请进来
Eagle Four to Lion One. Come in, please.
我们可能离得太远了  我不知道他们能否再接我们
We may be too far away. I don't know if they can pick us up anymore.
鹰四狮一  请进来
Eagle Four to Lion One. Come in, please.
狮子一号到鹰四号  -你在吗
- Lion One to Eagle Four. - Are you there?
是的  我们在这里  718-9.
Yes, we are here. 7-187-9.
192724.
首先给他们这些坐标
Give them these coordinates first.
告诉他们我想在1030的第二组坐标上集合
Tell them I want a rendezvous on the second set of coordinates at 1030.
我们正在南部通过4123-2179
We are proceeding south passing at 4123-2179.
你能安排在4128到2185与我们会合吗
Can you arrange a rendezvous with us at 4128-2185?
这会让我们做些什么  但是我们会试着在那里找到一个潜艇
It will tak e some doing, but we'll try to have one of our subs there.
你的ETA是多少
What is your ETA?
1030小时
1030 hours.
很好  再见
Very good. Cheerio.
干得好  Yelena
Good job, Yelena.
你知道  如果运气好的话  下星期我可以在伦敦给你买一杯饮料
You know, with any luck, I'll be able to buy you a drink in London next week.
在伦敦喝一杯真是太好了
It would be nice to have a drink in London.
自从蜜月以来我就没去过那儿
I haven't been there since my honeymoon.
好像是一千年前的事了  那是多久以前的事了
Seems like a thousand years ago. How long ago was it?
七年  你丈夫呢
Seven years. And your husband?
在战争的第一周被德国人杀害
Killed by the Germans in the first week of the war.
那么  你家里其他人呢
Well, how about the rest of your family?
他们中的一些人死了
Some of them are dead.
有些我不知道他们是死是活
Some I don't know if they're living or dead.
我哥哥  嗯…
My brother, well...
你知道我弟弟一定发生了什么事
You know what must have happened to my brother.
是的  我知道
Yes, I know.
好吧  你为什么不跟我们一起去呢
Well, look, why don't you come with us.
我的意思是  他们在伦敦流放了一个南斯拉夫政府
I mean, they got a Yugoslav government-in-exile in London.
你知道  他们会让你工作的
You know, they'll put you to work.
然后你可以在战后回来这里
And then you can come back here after the war.
当你这么说的时候  少校  我相信你最好相信它
When you say it, major, I believe lt. You better believe it.
嘿  少校  这些家伙大部分的英语说得比我好
Hey, major, most of these guys speak better English than I do.
是啊  别担心  看看他们发生了什么事
Yeah? Don't worry. Look what happened to them.
埃切瓦里  少校
Echevarria? Major.
你怎么样了  乔
And how you doing, Joe?
如果我有选择和你一起去Balkans旅游的话  少校
If I had my choice between touring the Balkans with you, major,
或者在巴黎经营一家夜总会
or running a nightclub in Paris,
叫我  Show Biz夜店先生
call me "Mr. Show Biz."
嗯  你会没事的
Hmm. You'll be all right.
好的  联系第十二亚历山大市的指挥官
All right, contact the commanding officer of the 12th at Alexandria.
告诉他立即对那列火车发动攻击
Tell him to execute an immediate attack on that train.
告诉他把它完全拿出来
Tell him to take it out completely.
杀死任何可见的东西
Kill anything in sight.
很好  先生
Very good, sir.
将军  你知道  我还不是莱特少校的崇拜者
General, as you know, I haven't been a great admirer of Major Wright,
但我相信他和他的部下有一个很好的尝试
but I'm sure he and his men had a damn good try.
哦  你真是太好了  上校
Well, that's damn nice of you, colonel.
但是时间是……对不起  将军
- But time is of... - Excuse me, general.
我们刚刚收到英国潜艇狮子一号的消息
We have just received word from the British submarine Lion One.
莱特少校袭击了保加利亚Sofia郊外的火车
Major Wright has attacked the train just outside of Sofia, Bulgaria,
在去爱琴海的路上
and is on his way to the Aegean.
好吧
All right!
你知道  少校  可能有12位高级党员
You know, major, there may be 12 high-ranking party members
或政府官员在那列火车上
or government officials upon that train.
是的  将军
Yes, general.
如果我呼吁停火和谈判
If I call for a cease-fire and negotiations,
在我发出命令之前  你不会采取任何行动
you will take no further actions until I give the command.
将军  我理解
I understand, general.
最重要的是  当然要拯救我们的人
The prime concern, of course, is to rescue our men.
第二个问题是确定
The second concern is to make sure
没有一个该死的美国人活着离开这里
that none of these damned Americans leave here alive.
他们在那儿  警官
There they are, sergeant.
All right, spread the word.
让所有人下车  前进  移动它
Get everybody off the train. Go ahead. Move it.
2420纳粹怎么样
What about the Nazis in 2420?
他们想要火车  我们要给他们
They wanted the train, we're gonna give it to them.
好吧  大家下车
All right, everybody out and off the train.
快点  跳下来
Come on, jump down!
开始射击
Commence firing!
走吧
Let's go!
好吧  Dravko  我们走吧
All right, Dravko, let's go.
把它们擦掉
Wipe them out!
去拿枪
Get to your gun!
我总是告诉你别紧张  肖蒂
I was always telling you to take it easy, Shorty.
好的  中士
All right, sergeant.
德国人将在15分钟内在这里增援
The Germans will have reinforcements here in 15 minutes.
让我们离开这里  和潜艇连接起来
Let's get out of here and link up with the sub.
我不和你一起去
I'm not going with you.
我不能  你在说什么
I can't. What are you talking about?
我的意思是  后面什么都没有
I mean, there's nothing for you back there.
哦  是的  有
Oh, yes, there is.
我给你走的每一个理由也是留下的理由
Every reason that I gave you to go is also a reason to stay.
我的丈夫  我的兄弟  我的整个家庭
My husband, my brother, my whole family.
同志们
My comrades.
我的生活就在这里  永远
My life is here, always.
你要去哪里  回到南斯拉夫
Where would you go? Back to Yugoslavia
加入蒂托的游击队
to join Tito's Partisans.
你会回来的
You will come back.
告诉我你会回来的
Tell me that you will come back.
该死的
Damn right.
让我们把它搬出去
Let's move it out.
我们走吧  士兵
Let's go, soldier!